Locke  你快写点东西
Locke, do you have a message
带上竹筏去的
to go on the raft?
等他们获救时
For when they get rescued.
他们就可以跟你家人联系了
They can contact your family.
Michael  Jin
我们当时在从悉尼飞往洛杉矶的飞机上
We were on a plane.Sydney to Los Angeles.
是815航班
Flight 815?
你也在飞机上
Right.
退后
Back up!
来人啊
Coming out.
声明: 本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
欢迎访问官方论坛  www.YYeTs.net 在线观看 剧情讨论 学习交流
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：Singa校对：扣扣
后期：xyz 双语制作： 胖丫头  youko  七色九天
========== 字幕总监制：七色九天 ==========
你好啊  Hurley
Hi, there, Hurley!
Jin  你回来了
Jin, you're here.
是的
I sure am.
伙计  你会说英语
Dude, you speak English.
不  是你在说韩语
No. You're speaking Korean.
是么?
他在这儿干什么?
一切都会改变的
Everything's going to change.
什么?
一切都会改变的
Everything's going to change.
来点咯咯鸡快餐吧  Hugo
Have a "cluckety-cluck-cluck" day, Hugo.
Hurley
你睡着了?
You fell asleep?
不  我只是...
No. I was just...
休息一下眼睛
resting my eyes.
那些数字写在这儿
The numbers are written right there.
好  我记得那些数字
Yeah. I remember the numbers.
Lock回去海滩那儿了
Locke went back to the beach,
下一个我来
so I'll be taking the next shift.
太好了
Awesome.
Jack告诉我你工作的事了
Jack told me about your job.
至少现在咱们又有工作了  是吧
At least we have jobs again, right?
太棒了
Hooray for us.
生活真不错呀
Well, ain't life grand?
现在要是有杯水就更好了
What I wouldn't give for a cup of water right now...
好了  别再叠罗汉了
No way. No more human pyramids.
省省吧
Just forget it.
让我们出去
Hey! Let us out of here!
-够了  冷静点
-Enough! Just chill!
我在这里的每一分钟
Every minute I spend down here
就是我儿子在危险之中的一分钟
is another minute my boy is still out there.
让我说给你听  Mikey
let me break it down for ya, Mikey.
现在Rambina他们一伙人
Right now,Rambina and her buddies
正在琢磨怎么对付我们
are trying to figure out what to do with us,
在他们决定之前
so until they make up their damn mind,
我们什么也做不了
there ain't nothing we can do.
对啊
Yeah.
要不你撒点尿在上面
Why don't you pee on it?
抓住绳子
Grab the rope.
拜托
Please.
别听他的
Don't do it.
沿绳子爬上来  不然我就朝你朋友开枪
Climb the rope, or I shoot your friend.
下一个是你
You next.
别上去
Don't do it.
她在骗我们
She's bluffing.
枪里只有一发子弹  她不会浪费在我们身上的
Gun's only got one bullet, she ain't gonna waste it on...
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch!
妈的
God!
抓住绳子
Grab the rope.
下个是我吗  辣妹
You want me, Hot Lips?
这得要你下来...
You're gonna have to come down here and get...
婊子
Bitch.
4,8,15,16,23
特别号码  42
with the Mega Number 42.
如果有人买了这组数字就中了头彩
Whoever has those numbers has won
否则奖金将累计至下一期
or will share in a near-record jackpot.
是啊  Mary Jo
That's right, Mary Jo,
已经连续有16期没有产生大奖了
because this is the 16th week without a winner.
Hugo
Hugo  Hugo
Hugo  醒醒
Hugo, wake up!
醒醒
Wake up!
好了  妈妈  好了  我只是滑倒了
Stop! Ma, stop! I just slipped.
坐着都会滑倒  是心脏不好么
Slipped, sitting down? Is it your heart?
妈妈  我没事
Ma, I'm fine.
你在骗我
You're lying.
我知道  因为你眼睛没有看着我
I always know.You don't look me in the eyes.
我没骗你
I'm not lying.
那就告诉我发生了什么事
Then tell me what happened.
一定是我吃东西吃坏了
It must have been something I ate.
是的  一定是你吃坏了
Yes, something you ate,
因为你吃这么多东西却从不运动
because you eat basura, and you don't exercise.
我做运动
I do exercise.
滑倒不叫运动
Falling down is not exercise.
你唯一做的运动
The only time you move
就是拿着食物往口里塞
is to lift a drumstick from the bucket.
每天都一样  Hugo
Every day it's the same thing. Hugo.
工作  看电视  然后吃鸡肉
Work, TV, chicken.
你得改变一下你的生活了  Hugo
You have to change your life, Hugo.
你认为别人会帮你改变吗
You think someone else will change it for you?
如果你每天都在祈祷还有可能
Maybe if you pray every day
耶稣会从天堂下来
Jesus Christ will come down,
帮你减掉200磅然后带给你一个不错的女人
take 200 pounds and bring you a decent woman.
还有一辆新车
And a new car.
是的  耶稣会给你一辆新车的
Yes, Jesus can bring you a new car.
也许我不想改变  也许我喜欢我的生活
Maybe I don't wanna change. Maybe I like my life.
一定是耶稣打来的
That must be Jesus.
是的  是耶稣打来的
Yes, it is Jesus!
他想知道你要什么颜色的车
He wants to know what color car you want!
Hurley  打扰一下
Hurley! All right, mate?
我们得聊一下
We need to have a little chat.
别担心  他妈妈散步去了
Don't worry! Mummy's off for a walk,
所以现在只有你我和这个孩子
so it's just you, me, and the baby.
说一下吧
Spill it.
说什么
Spill what?
那个舱子
The hatch.
里面有什么
What's in it?
什么也没有  真的
Nothing, really.
你在那儿整整一天一夜了
You've been out there an entire day and night.
什么都没看到
Looking at nothing?
我想它就像...
Well, I guess...
一个掩体
it's kind of like a bunker.
你知道  是二战时的
You know, from World War Two?
可能还要晚一点
Only newer.
里面有什么?
And what's in it?
我不知道
I don't know.
但是无论如何你知道那是一个掩体
But somehow you know it's a bunker.
我想是别人告诉我的
Well, I guess someone told me?
你要骗我?
You're gonna lie to me?
你要骗这孩子?
You're gonna lie to the baby?
伙计  听着  我从不说谎
Dude, look, I'd never lie.
那你上次还跟我说你有1亿5千万的家产
And the time you told me you were worth $150 million?
是1亿5千6百万
It's 156 million.
抱歉  我可能为我900万亿的家产
I'm sorry! I must've confused it
感到困惑了
with the 900 trillion I am worth myself!
这孩子是巧克力棒棒糖做的
And this baby's made of chocolate lollipops,
还有如果你不介意的话
so excuse us,
我会拍拍翅膀飞离这个岛
I'm going to flap my wings and fly off this island.
嘿  Rose
Hey, Rose.
你好
Hey, yourself.
那个  在洗衣服啊
So, doing laundry, huh?
是啊
Indeed I am.
帮我把那些脏衣服递过来吧
You wanna hand me those dirty clothes over there?
谢谢
Thank you.
你不想知道发生了什么吗
Don't you wanna know what happened?
发生什么了
What happened?
你知道  就在那里
You know... out there.
每个人都问我舱子里有什么
Everyone's asking me what's in the hatch.
那是你自己的事  亲爱的
Well, that's your business, honey.
你不想知道
Don't you wanna know?
不管是什么  它都不会
Well, whatever it is, it's not going to help
帮我洗衣服的  是吧
get this laundry done now, is it?
事实上
Well, actually,
可能会的
it sort of is.
就在这附近
It's around here somewhere...
真的有人住在这下面吗
Someone actually lived down here
这是用来干什么的
Well, what is it for?
这...
It's...
这说来话长
t's kind of a long story.
Hurley...
你还告诉谁了
Who else did you tell?
没了
No one.
我发誓
I swear.
伙计  这工作量太大
Dude, it's a big job.
我需要...
I needed...
帮助
help.
你好  Jack  -你好  Rose
-Hello, Jack. -Hey, Rose.
她很好  她不会和别人说的
She's cool. She won't tell anyone.
亲爱的  我连我要说什么都不知道了
Honey, I don't even know what I would say.
这全是吃的吗
All this is food?
这只是个时间问题
It's only a matter of time before
他们迟早会知道我们在这儿找到什么的
we have to tell everyone what we found.
那么  你知道该怎么做了
So, you know what to do?
清点一下所有食物
Inventory all of it,
算一下能维持多久
and figure out how we make it last.
这期间不许有人拿东西吃
And in the meantime, nobody gets anything.
没人可以例外
No exceptions.
你就负责这个Hurley  行吗
That's your responsibility,Hurley. OK?
-什么声音  -你不会想要知道的
-What's that? -You don't wanna know.
达摩启动计划色拉调料
"Dharma Initiative salad dressing:
农场合成风味
Ranch composite. "
听起来很美味
That sounds tasty.
"阿波罗条"你听说过吗
"Apollo Bars?" You ever hear of these?
但是糖就是糖  Bernard经常这么说的
But candy is candy. That's what Bernard always says.
说到吃甜品
Talk about a sweet tooth.
那家伙真的很爱吃甜的东西
That man has a mouth full of sweet teeth.
Bernard  是你的丈夫
Bernard. That was your husband?
是我的丈夫
"Is" my husband.
但是...
But...
我还以为他当时是在飞机的后舱
I thought he was in the back of the plane?
抱歉  我不是说...
I'm sorry, I didn't mean...
不  没关系  没事的
No, that's OK, don't feel bad.
Bernard肯定还活着  我知道的
Bernard is fine. I know it.
你想拿走这罐金枪鱼么
You wanna get the canned tuna?
每个人都会恨我的  Rose
Everyone's gonna hate me, Rose.
别傻了
Now, that's just plain silly.
你可能是唯一一个
You're about the only one on this island
岛上的人全都喜欢的人了
that everybody loves.
那是会改变的
Well, that'll change.
你们在这儿有看到过香波没
You happen to find any shampoo in here?
是的  那儿有几瓶
Yeah, there's some right over here.
Kate  你不能拿...
Kate, you can't take it...
谢谢  Hurley
Thanks, Hurley.
只是一瓶罢了
It's just one bottle.
有人拿了大家都会来拿的
That's where it starts.
欢迎来到咯咯鸡快餐店  你想要点什么
Welcome to Mr Cluck's, can I take your order?
嘿  Hugo
Hey, Hugo.
你还好吧  伙计
You OK, man?
很好
Yeah.
没事
Fine.
Reyes  马上来我办公室
Reyes! My office! Now!
有什么要说的么  Reyes
You wanna tell me something, Reyes?
没有
No.
你确定
You sure about that?
是的
Yeah.
这是昨晚的监控录像
This is last night's surveillance tape.
Reyes  你欠公司
Reyes, you owe the company
8块黑肉三明治
for an eight-piece dark-meat combo.
-我没吃8块这么多  -你想把录像都看一遍吗
-I didn't eat eight.  -You want to watch the whole tape?
你在这儿的时候
Oh, and while you're here:
我和你说了几次了
How many times do I gotta tell you
那些餐巾纸是要钱的  好吗
those napkins cost money, all right?
每个客人只能给两张  就两张  我们不是
It's two per customer. Two. We're not
我们咯咯鸡快餐店是不印钱的  Reyes
We're not made of money here at Mr Cluck's, Reyes.
我不是家财万贯  你是吗
I'm not made of money. Are you made of money?
因为如果你家财万贯
If you're made of money,
可能你就不会在这儿工作了  所以好好想想
maybe you don't want to work here. So,get it together.
怎么了  有问题吗  Reyes
What, is that a problem, Reyes?
伙计  我不干了
Dude, I quit.
哦  天那
Oh, my God.
-哦  天那  -伙计
-Oh, my God.  -Dude?
你没事吧?
Are you OK?
我... 我很好
I... I'm fine.
Randy情绪很失控
Randy is losing his brain in there!
你最好回去
You should get back in
否则他会让你在这周剩余的时间里都去打扫厕所
or he'll make you scrub johns all week.
-不可能了  我也不干了  -什么
-Doubt it. I quit too. -What?
看来我们都可以休假一天了
Looks like we got ourselves a day off.
我都长这么帅了还要钱干吗
Who needs money when you got good looks?
你现在可以出来了
You can come out now.
我在岩石那儿看到你了
I saw you back at the rock.
在红树那儿也是
Then at the mangrove tree.
事实上  我绕了一个大圈
In fact, I've walked in a big circle.
我不明白你怎么都没看出来
I'm not sure how you didn't realise it.
好吧
All right,
你不需要讽刺我
you don't have to insult me.
想告诉我为什么跟着我吗  Charlie
Want to tell me why you've been following me, Charlie?
好吧
Yeah.
原因很简单  John
Quite simply, John,
这地方有太多的秘密
there are a lot of secrets around here.
我也厌烦了只是看护着那孩子
And I'm tired of being at the kids' table.
我把Claire的孩子带回来了
I got Claire's baby back!
但却没有和你们一起行动
I didn't go to the Black Rock
去黑岩石那儿
on the A-Team mission,
但是如果有人要我去我肯定会去的
but I would have, if someone had asked me.
我想我有资格知道这里的一些事情
I think I'm entitled to some sodding answers around here.
你想知道什么
What do you want to know?
进展怎么样了
How's it going?
还不行
It's not.
这门的另一边有更多的混凝土
On the other side of this door, there's more concrete.
我想至少有8到10英尺厚
I'd say it's at least eight-to-ten-feet thick.
你看见了吗
Did you see this?
有意思
Interesting.
还好这是钛合金
Good thing this is titanium.
基本上没什么磁性
Almost no magnetic attraction.
但是我们不能从上面过去
we're not going to get in up here.
从上面
Up here
也许我们可以从下面走
Perhaps we can go under it.
抓住绳子
Grab the rope.
在我知道我的朋友们没事前我什么也不会做
I ain't doing nothing until I know my friends are OK.
那我们现在是朋友了吧
So we're friends now, huh?
快上来  不然我把绳子拉上来了
Do it now or the rope comes up.
你们好啊  朋友们
Howdy, boys,
-谢谢你们救我  -没事了
-thanks for the rescue.  -Everything is cool,
我们谈过了
we had a talk,
他们相信了我们也是在飞机上的
and they believe we were on the plane, too.
又多了一批幸存者
Swell.
我猜我们可以一起去告大洋航空公司了
I guess we can all sue Oceanic together.
你手上的是什么?
What you got there?
没什么
Nothing.
是石头么  你想报复我
You got a rock? Looking for some revenge?
-给你3秒钟时间丢了它  -Ana
-You got three seconds to drop it.  -Ana.
等下...喔
Now, hold on...
嘿  怎么...
Hey, what's...
你还没说3
You didn't say "three".
闭嘴
Shut up.
我叫你做什么就做什么
When I tell you to do something, you do it.
我叫你走你就走  我叫你停你就停
I say move, you move. I say stop, you stop.
-我说跳  你怎么做  -你先跳
-I say jump, what do you say?  -"You first. "
你如果不按我说的做
You don't like the rules,
我现在就把你一屁股踢回那个坑里
I toss your ass back in the pit right now.
知道了么
You understand?
知道了
I understand.
天色开始暗了
It's getting dark.
我们得出发了
We're moving out.
出发去哪儿
Moving out where?
我刚说了什么
What did I just tell you?
抱歉  我忘了
Sorry. Forgot.
不过还有一件事
Just one thing, though.
你再打我一下
You hit me again,
我会杀了你
I'll kill you.
我们出发
Let's go.
他每隔108分钟就要按那个键
He pushed that button every 108 minutes?
是的
He did indeed.
但是这怎么可能  我是说  他不用睡觉
How is that possible? I mean,didn't he sleep?
不知道  没机会问他
Don't know. I didn't get a chance to ask him.
那之后  他上来然后离开了
After all that time, he just up and left?
我是说为什么  他会去哪
I mean why? Where'd he go?
不知道
Don't know.
我试图跟踪他  但是他并没有留下太多的痕迹
I tried to track him, but he didn't leave much of a trail.
我想他认为他已经找到了他的替代者
I guess he'd found his replacements.
-是指我们  -是我们
-Meaning us?  -Meaning us.
这听起来有点疯狂
It sounds a bit... nutty,
不是么
doesn't it?
但事实就是那样的  Charlie
It is what it is, Charlie.
如果我们不按那颗键会发生什么
And what happens if we don't push it?
我们不会去找答案的  我正在建立一个制度
We're not going to find out. I'm setting up a system.
具体还没弄好  大概框架是
I'm still working on it, but looks like
-我们要每2个人一班值6个小时的岗  -轮换
-two-person shifts every six hours or so.  -Shifts.
按按键
Pushing a button?
那儿还有只电唱机
Oh, and there's a record player.
Hurley在那儿干什么
What's Hurley been doing there?
他主管食物
He's in charge of the food.
食物
Food?
嘿  伙计
Hey, mate.
你去哪儿了
Where have you been?
嘿  我...在附近转了转
Hey. I've been... around.
我知道了  Hurley
I know, Hurley.
知道什么
You know what?
我知道关于食物的事了  Locke把一切都告诉我了
I know about the food. Locke told me everything.
-知道吗Locke在骗你  -我知道
-You kown Locke's lying.  -I am.
他骗我说我们得每隔108分钟按一下按键
Did you lie about the button we have to push every 108 minutes
不然这个岛就会爆炸
or the island explodes?
不会爆炸的
It's not gonna explode.
-拜托  -听着  是Jack让我来管理的
-Come on. -Look, Jack put me in charge.
-我其实并不想...  -那有花生酱吗
-I don't even want to...  -Is there peanut butter?
什么
What?
花生酱
Peanut butter.
果仁的  奶油的  能够吸引孩子的那种
Nutty? Creamy? Staple of children everywhere?
是的  有一些
Yeah, a couple jars.
好极了  给我们一罐怎么样
Brilliant. How about you give us one?
是给Claire的
It's for Claire.
不行  伙计
No can do, man.
你对一个正在抚养婴儿的母亲说不
You're saying no to a nursing mother?
-不是这样的  -就是这样的
-It's not like that.  -It's exactly like that.
你看  我从没想过会这样  但是事实就是如此
You kown, I never thought this would happen, but it did.
-你变成了他们的一员  -他们的一员
-You've become one of them.  -One of them?
他们  那些人  那些领导
Them. The man. Management.
我还以为我们是朋友
I thought we were friends.
你变了  伙计
You've changed, man.
主动轴乐队... 不比糟糕乐队好多少
Drive Shaft... More like Suck Shaft.
我去看看那些耳机
I'm gonna go to check out the headphones.
好的  耳机
Sure. Headphones.
Hugo  -Starla
你们这两个笨蛋怎么没上班
Why aren't you chuckleheads at work?
我们正在找其他的工作
We're currently exploring other opportunities.
你辞职了
You quit?
是的
I did.
他今天和老板吵架了  他出轨了
He's mixing it up today. He's off the rails.
谁能看紧他
Somebody get a straightjacket!
我能试试那些吗
Hey, can I try those on?
你正在颠覆我的世界观  Hugo
You're messing with my world-view.
你让我震惊
You're my rock.
我是说  你辞职了就像
I mean, if you quit your job,
蜜蜂不采蜜了一样
the next thing you know, bees will stop making honey,
花儿会死的
and flowers will die,
而且  这音响也会掉下去摔成两半
and, hell, the whole damn thing will fall apart.
那么  Starla...
So, Starla...
抱歉
Sorry.
海德剧院这个周末有民谣歌手表演
The Hold Steady's playing the Troubadour this weekend.
我在想周五是否...
And I was wondering, maybe Friday...
我得上班
Oh, I have to work.
不  我不是说...
Oh, no, I didn't mean...
星期六我可以去  可以么
I can probably go Saturday. That cool?
好  太好了
Yeah. That's totally cool.
伙计  你准备追这女孩都已经一个月了
Dude, you've been crushing on her for months.
而你却什么都没做
and doing nothing.
今天你做到了
Today, you're fricking Fabio!
认真的说  伙计  你到底在想什么
Seriously, man, what has gotten into you?
没什么  我只是在那个以前想约她出去...
Nothing. I just wanted to ask her out before...
在什么以前
Before what?
没什么
Nothing.
这是最后一段管道
This is the last duct.
我想我们正在开始的那堵墙的下面
I believe we're under the area where we began.
他们连这里都浇灌了混凝土
They've poured concrete all the way down here, too.
也很厚
Just as thick.
也许附近还有路
Maybe there's a way around it.
这些东西都是用来干什么的
What is all this stuff?
要我猜
My best guess?
墙后有一台地热发电机
There's a geothermal generator behind this wall.
那就是能量的源头
That's the power source.
小心这些管子
Careful with these pipes.
它们非常烫
They are very hot.
没路了
That's it. Nothing.
这里堵住了
It's blocked.
你认为怎么样  Sayid
So, what do you think, Sayid?
什么认为怎么样  Jack?
What do I think about what, Jack?
这个地方  那台电脑
This place, the computer.
你认为到底怎么回事
What do you think is going on?
我上次听说像这里这样
The last time I heard of concrete
把混凝土到处浇灌的地方...
being poured over everything in this way...
是在切尔诺贝利
was Chernobyl.
你撞到什么了么
Did you hit something?
我想没有
I don't think so.
声音是从那里传过来的
It's coming from over there.
我去看看
I'm gonna check it out.
你...你在淋浴
You...You took a shower.
我想看看这还能不能用
Had to see if it worked.
怎么样
How was it?
水压有点问题
Pressure sucked
而且有时会突然变冷
and it kind of went cold at one point,
水闻起来有一点硫磺的味道
and it smelled a little bit like sulphur,
但是多少还是把澡给洗了
but it was a shower.
是啊  我懂你意思
Yeah. I know what you mean.
你也可以来冲一个
You could use one.
过会儿好了
Maybe a little later.
给你留了香波
I'll leave the shampoo for you.
我是Libby
I'm Libby.
我叫Michael
Michael.
你们有多少人
How many of you?
我是说  在岛的另一边
You know, on the other side of the island?
我们离开时  大概有40个
When we left, around 40.
你们幸存了多少人
How many of you survived?
23个
Twenty-three of us.
你还好吗
Are you all right?
你现在倒关心起我来了
Now you give a damn.
我说了很抱歉  那是一场误会
I said I'm sorry. It was a misunderstanding.
当我要冰爽茶  而你给我的是柠檬汁
A misunderstanding is when you bring me lemonade
这才叫误会
instead of iced tea.
我说过不准说话
I said no talking.
是他在和我说话
He was talking to me!
我们到了
We're here.
你想干什么  把我们绑柱子上
What are you gonna do, beam us up?
我记得你说你们有23个人
I thought you said there were 23 of you.
以前是的
There were.
怎么了
What's wrong?
我  我在海里发现了个东西
I, I found something out in the water.
我告诉了Shannon
And I told Shannon about it,
然后我们认为应该和你说一下
and we thought you should know...
这是竹筏上的那个漂流瓶
It's the messages from the raft.
我们想你应该决定做些什么
We thought you should decide what to do.
你为什么要告诉Charlie  伙计
Why did you tell Charlie, man?
-是他问我的  Hugo  -但你不应该告诉他
-Because he asked, Hugo.  -You shouldn't have.
你应该下来听听我的意见
You should have listened to me about coming down here.
现在一切都会改变了  一切
Now,It's all gonna change. Everything.
改变是好事  Hugo
Change is good, Hugo.
人人都这么说  但那不是真的  伙计
You know, people say that, but it's not true, man.
相信我  我很清楚
Trust me, I know.
猜猜谁会成为坏人
And guess who gets to be the bad guy?
谁会想说"不  你不能拿走那罐
Who says "No, you can't have peanut butter
给那可爱的金发女人和她可怜的婴儿的花生酱"?
for the cute blonde and her poor island baby. "
你知道是谁吗  是我
You know who? It's me.
你知道吗  我不想干这个了
You know what? I'm not gonna do it.
找其他人来做吧  伙计
Find someone else to deal with the chow, man.
不  我们都有自己该干的事  Hugo
No, we all have our jobs, Hugo.
我的工作是在人们不知道为什么的情况下
My job is to convince people to push a button every 108 minutes
说服他们每隔108分钟按一下按键
without them knowing why or for what.
-想交换么  -我不想干这个了
-Wanna trade?  -I don't wanna do this, man.
我也曾经有很多我不愿意做的事
I've had lots of jobs I didn't want to do.
但我还是做了
But I still did them.
我很抱歉  Hugo
I'm sorry, Hugo,
你要继续做下去
you don't get to quit.
那好吧
OK, then.
小心点
Be careful!
知道了
Dude. I am.
你拿到了吗?
You got it?
拿到了
Yeah, I got it.
好的  我们走
All right. Let's go!
你想我们玩偶拿得够多了吧?
Do you think we got enough gnomes?
是的  我们干得很棒
We're good.
真是太聪明了
This is genius.
不  不是左边  伙计  角度再大点
No, no, to the left, dude. More of an angle.
快跑
Run!
笨蛋
CLUCK YOU
自由了
Freedom!
-伙计  你在干什么  -我们自由了
-Dude, what are you doing?  -Freedom!
那么  你今晚还想做些什么吗
So, anything else you wanna do tonight?
你最好让我知道
You'd better let me know now,
因为我们一天的休假马上就要结束了  Hugo老兄
because our day off is just about over, Huggy Bear.
10小时后
In about ten hours
我们就得为自己找一份新的工作
we're gonna have to find ourselves some new employment.
我听说比萨店正在招人
I hear Pizza Bin is hiring.
我们可以去Gyrorama碰碰运气
Or we could try our luck at Gyro-rama.
我很喜欢在那工作的漂亮的小妞
I do kind of dig the chick who works at the Bin.
伙计  答应我一些事
Dude, promise me something.
好的  什么?
OK, what?
答应我不论发生了什么
Promise me that no matter what happens,
我们都不要改变...
we'll never change.
永远不要改变
This'll never change.
好的
OK.
噢  我知道是怎么回事了
Oh! I know what this is about.
我知道你最近为什么这么怪了
I know why you've been acting so weird lately.
你要去做那个  呃... 那个  呃...
You're getting that stomach-stapling
胃分离手术之类的  不是么
surgery thing, aren't you?
-我是不会去做手术的  -没事  伙计  这不错的
-I'm not getting surgery.  -Come on, it's cool.
我是说  我仍然可以装做大吃一惊
I mean, I can still be all surprised,
就像"哦  天那  Hurley  真的是你么?"
I can be like, "Ooh, my, Hurley. Wow, is that you?"
听着Johnny  我是认真的
Listen, Johnny, I'm serious.
答应我  我和你永远要维持原状
Promise me that you and I will always stay the same.
我还有更好的
I'll do you one better.
我不止要维持原状  兄弟
Not only will I stay gold, Ponyboy,
我还要为此干一杯
I will drink to it.
我能借2块钱吗
Can I borrow two bucks?
你在干什么  Hurley
What you got there, Hurley?
这是炸药
It's dynamite.
炸药  你弄来干什么
Dynamite? Well, what are you doing with it?
抱歉  我不能让它再发生了
I'm sorry. But I can't let it happen again.
这儿为什么会有记者
Why is there a news crew here?
伙计  我们不要去那里
Dude, we shouldn't go here.
伙计  我们走吧  他们只是在抬什么东西
Dude, let's go, they jack the prices here.
可能有人中枪了
Maybe somebody got shot.
你为什么这么做  亲爱的
Why are you doing this, honey?
听着  快出去  Rose
Look, just get out of here, Rose.
但是你会伤到人的
But you're gonna hurt somebody.
我不会在门外弄的
Not if I do it from outside the door.
这门很厚
It's thick.
而且我会首先确定附近没人的
And I'll make sure there's nobody around first.
所以拜托你先出去好么
So, please, will you just go?
哼哼  是你把我从海滩拉起来
Uh-uh. You haul me off the beach
这么大老远拖来这个地方的
and you drag me into this place,
那么至少在你引爆前
at least I can get is an explanation
能给我个解释吧
before you blow it up.
你不会懂的
You don't get it.
这地方会把事情弄得一团糟
This is gonna mess it all up!
伙计  有人中彩票了
Dude! Somebody won the lottery!
让我告诉你吧  Rose
Let me tell you something, Rose.
我们以前都相处得很好  直到我们有了...
We were all fine before we had
马铃薯片
any potato chips.
当我们有了这些薯片后
Now we've got these potato chips,
每个人都想得到它
everyone's gonna want them.
Steve拿了它们  Charlie不高兴了
So, Steve gets them, Charlie's pissed,
但他没有向Steve发火  他是在生我的气
but not pissed at Steve, he's pissed at me.
就是那个人
That's the guy!
就是他
我就成了大家的目标
And I'm gonna be in the middle of it.
然后就会有人叫"我们的呢?"
And then it's gonna be, "What about us?"
"我怎么没有薯片?"
"Why didn't I get any potato chips?"
"拜托  帮帮我们  Hurley"
"Come on, help us out, Hurley."
"那你为什么把香波给了Kate?"
"Why did you give Kate the shampoo?"
"而我却拿不到花生酱?"
"Why didn't I get the peanut butter?"
然后他们就会变得疯狂起来  追问道
Then, they'll get really mad and start asking,
"为什么这些东西都是Hugo的"
"Why does Hugo have everything?"
"为什么是他来决定分配?"
"Why should he get to decide?"
然后他们都会恨我
Then they'll all hate me.
我不知道该怎么办
I don't know what to do.
食物清单都列好了  这是唯一的办法
Jack, the inventory's done. This is the only way.
你是认真的
Are you serious
伙计  那儿的食物够一个人
Dude, there's enough food in there
一天吃三顿并且维持三个月
to feed one guy three meals a day for another three months.
我们有40个人  这点食物一点不够
We have 40 people. It's just not gonna work.
听着  你让我来管的话 这件事只能这么做了
Look, you put me in charge, this is what we're doing.
好的
OK.
OK?
是的  好的
Yeah. OK.
好的
OK.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
你们来的那里
Back where you guys,
那群人里
where you came from...
有一个叫Rose的女人吗
is there a woman named Rose there?
50多岁的黑人?
Black chick in her fifties?
她...
Is she...
她还好么?
is she OK?
是的  伙计
Yeah, man.
她很好
She's OK.
谢谢
Oh, thank you.
Michael  我叫Michael
Michael. I'm Michael.
谢谢你  Michael
Thank you, Michael.
我叫Bernard
I'm Bernard.
好了
OK.
没事的  她很好
It's OK. She's good.
==============|  YYeTs字幕组招募启示  |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国)  双语字幕校正   时间轴调整
英语翻译   欧美影视新闻翻译  影视评论  论坛版主  美工人员
服务器提供者  发布宣传  联系地址：www.YYeTs.com
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报酬 ====